choxi.com 2019-12-07

# jClub.com: Great deals on Electronics, Jewelry, Lifestyle, Men, Women, Pets, Kids & more

J Club, Inc. (“jClub”, the “Company”, “we”, or “us”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared. We take your privacy seriously and want to outline the measures we take in safe guarding your personal information, the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. By visiting the jClub website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, or mobile application services offered from time to time by the Company in connection therewith (collectively, the “Website”), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

The Privacy Policy covers the Company’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that the Company gathers when you are accessing the Company’s Website and when you use Company Services.

### Your Personal Information We Collect

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services, and to allow our users to set up a user profile and make purchases via the Website. In general, we use the personal information we collect from you to fulfill your order, send you an order confirmation, send you requested product or service information, respond to customer service requests, improve our Website and marketing efforts, display content based upon your interests and administer your account.

When you register or log in, you supply your email address and a password. This allows us to provide you access to your account every time you visit the Website. Before completing your first purchase, we also ask you for your name, phone number, email address, billing and shipping addresses. This information, along with your credit card number, is necessary to fulfill your order. This information may be disclosed to specific members of our staff and to select third parties (such as our credit card processor and party or parties shipping products you have ordered) involved in the completion of your transaction and delivery of your order. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features, and you may not be able to complete a purchase through the Website.

When you receive an e-mail from us, clicking on it or opening it shall constitute an affirmative opt-in to receive further emails from us. However, you can always opt-out for any reason as any time by following the instructions set forth below.

We may use your email address to notify you about deals offered by the Company (such as daily deals, special events or information, generally) or to inform you of your order placement, order status, and/or shipping information if you have opted-in. Emails are sent to Company users who have chosen to receive them (opted-in) or who have made a purchase on the Website. At any time, you can notify us to opt-out from receiving these emails (see “Opt-Out” Section below). In addition, we keep a record of your past purchases, returns, and credits. We may also ask you for information regarding your personal preferences and demographics to help us better meet your needs and improve the overall shopping experience on the Website. Further, we use marketing consultants to help us maintain and analyze our data and allow us to market more efficiently. They may use cookies or web beacons to collect information about you, in connection with providing you information via email or direct mail about products and services that might be of interest to you. You can choose not to have this information used by our trusted third party advertising partners by contacting us to opt out.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Website, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Website. The Company stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email (and tracking the success of our referral program). Your friend may contact us at [support@jclub.com](mailto:support@jclub.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

We may also display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Website and/or our social media accounts in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us using the information below.

Users of your Website are required to be at least 18 years old, and any user under 18 is not an authorized user. Additionally, if we learn that a user is under 13 years of age, we will promptly delete any Personal Information we have collected about that user.

### Automatically Collected Information

Upon engaging the Website or Company services, the Company automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, the type of browser being used, cookie information, the page you requested, duration of activity on our site, and any items you may purchase. This information may be used to customize the content you see on our Website or to communicate with you about special offers. These statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us with information regarding the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities of that user. We may make extensive use of this data at an aggregated level in order to understand how our Company Website is being used.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Like most other transactional websites, we use “cookies” to improve your shopping experience and to save you time. Cookies are little tags that are placed onto your computer. We assign a cookie to your computer when you first visit us in order to enable us to recognize you each time you return. Cookies allow us to customize our Website to your individual preferences in order to create a more personalized shopping experience. Please note that the cookies we use for our Website or email campaigns do not store personally identifiable information about your finances. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use some areas of our Website, such as the shopping cart, will be limited.

When we partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other sites, our ad network partners use cookies and Web Beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on the Website and other sites to provide you with targeted advertising based upon your interests. Clear figs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [HERE](https://out.jclub.com/unsubscribe) . Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

The use of tacking technologies by our service providers, technology partners, or other third party assets (such as social media) on the Website is not covered by this Privacy Policy. These third parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our Website. We do not have access to or control over these technologies. We do not tie the information gathered to our customers’ or users’ personally identifiable information.

### Sharing of Personal Information

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only in instances as described in this Privacy Policy.

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you, such as shipping your order, processing a payment, or offering customer service. Unless we tell you differently, the Company’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

We restrict access to your Personal Information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. At all times, we take the utmost care to protect your Personal Information.

The Company may be forced to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative, or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or when the Company, in its sole discretion, deems it necessary in order to protect its rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk, or to enforce or apply the Company’s Website Terms & Conditions.

If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information.

### Secure Shopping for All jClub Customers

The Company endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private. Your Company account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

When the Company’s order form asks users to enter Personal Information such as a credit card number, that information is encrypted with industry-standard Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) encryption to keep your online order safe and secure. The Company also maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at [support@jclub.com](mailto:support@jclub.com) . 

### User Access and Choice (Opt-Out)

If your Personal Information changes, you may correct, update, amend, remove, or ask to have it removed by making the change on your user account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at [support@jclub.com](mailto:support@jclub.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. If you no longer desire our service, or wish to have all your information deleted, please contact us directly. We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [support@jclub.com](mailto:support@jclub.com) . 

### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits individual California residents with whom the Company has a relationship to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To make such a request, please write to us at the address below or email us at [support@jclub.com](mailto:support@jclub.com) , with the subject line (either to our physical or email address) as “California Privacy Rights”. Please allow up to 20 business days for a response. 

### Third Party Links and Plug-Ins

Our Website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of the Company. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, links to our various social media pages and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Website. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Changes in Policy

The Company may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of the Terms & Conditions and you unconditionally agree that using this Website signifies your assent to the Terms & Conditions. Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions, including limitations on damages. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or by sending you an email at least 15 or 30 days prior to the change taking effect, respectively depending on the method of notice. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on the Website, please send us a detailed message to [support@jclub.com](mailto:support@jclub.com) and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns. You may also write us at: 

J Club, Inc.   
1200 Avenue of the Americas, 5th Floor   
New York, NY 10036   

_Effective Date: January 12, 2017_
